Juri Wollmann



linkedin.com/in/iuri-wollmann



https://iwollmann.github.io/



iurimw@outlook.com

Summary

I am a full-stack developer focused on the web with over 13 years of experience, most of them using the Microsoft .NET stack. I have already participated in projects that required many integrations, high availability, and resilience. Working remotely for a company based in the USA for the past 3 years.

My strength is the C# language I have worked with almost my entire career. I had the opportunity to work with people outside the curve, with enormous capacity and background and I learned a lot from them both in the way of working and thinking. And this is something that I try to aim for, to become someone that people can use as an example.

Right now, I aim at the Javascript stack (Node.js, React and React Native), so I'm currently doing some training and studying this stack a lot, because I really like how simple and light it is to work with this environment, so I'm looking for a position that allows me to work with at least one of these technologies.

One fact (outside of work) about me...

I am now involved in the GoStack training, a 6-week training from Rocketseat, that creates a complete, back-end, front-end and mobile application using TypeScript, Node.js, React and React Native. And I'm also participating in EDX training for the AWS Fundamentals, because this is a gap in my DevOps skillset.

My main goal now is to work immersed into other cultures, so I'm trying to improve my English speech with daily calls with my friends to practice. Another thing is that I'm preparing my documents to apply for my Italian citizenship.

Experience



Software Consultant

SAI Global

Feb 2017 - Present (3 years 3 months +)

Working remotly here.

Development of an authenticate portal using identity server 4 on backend and react at frontend.

Development of an application for build custom surveys using the surveyjs and integrating it with the in house system, all in react with redux and backend with c# using .net core.

Development of others applications integrated with the main platform company.

And currently working on an application that embed the powerbi reports and integrates with the main platform and the powerbi services.



Senior Software Developer

Concrete Solutions

Jul 2016 - Feb 2017 (8 months)

Test automation using ruby stack.

Helps in the development of SPA applications using react and node.js.

Software Developer

Modulo Security Solutions

Apr 2012 - Jun 2016 (4 years 3 months)

I worked on the company's main platform, maintaining and developing it, and also creating other applications and services integrated with it.

Here I had the opportunity to learn about multitenancy, scalability, availability and resilience.

This platform is huge, has many modules and services and integrates with other external services.



IT Consultant

Ibrowse Consultoria e Informática

Oct 2011 - Apr 2012 (7 months)

Maintain and develop new features for PNAD-C, IBGE`s system responsible for collect and summarize characteristics and socioeconomics data about the population.

MODULO Software Developer

Modulo Security Solutions

Nov 2006 - Sep 2011 (4 years 11 months)

I started in Modulo Security developing and maintaining the software used internally. In that period I had contact with several programming languages (JSP, Vb.Net, classic ASP, PHP and C#) and several databases (MySql, SQLServer and Oracle).

I played many roles, from the simple developer to the coordinator of the area, responsible even for the hiring of new collaborators.

During this period I had the opportunity to work on many projects: company website, ERP integrations, ERP migration, timesheet system, software migration in vb.net for c#, mail marketing system and several others.

Experience is what I didn't miss, I made mistakes and hit right too, but certainly had more success, since I started as a trainee and I left the company as a developer of the RiskManager platform, where I also had the opportunity to cover almost all the modules that make up the platform.

Education



Estácio

Bachelor of System Analysis 2004 - 2008

Licenses & Certifications



Machine Learning - Coursera

TG986V9F6STC



Divide and Conquer, Sorting and Searching, and Randomized Algorithms - Coursera G2QV6XU7SHLC

Skills

C# • MVC • JavaScript • TypeScript • React.js • Node.js • .NET Core • Redux.js • SQL • GraphQL